Ghost Meets Gal!
All of you who chose my lesson,
a wise decision!
Sergeant Serjean
Dance Instructor
I'll turn you all into fine soldiers
with my military-style dance training!
Finally, the lessons start today.
I'm gonna give it my all.
Santhi!
Present~
Lubna!
Hm? I don't see them anywhere.
Are they absent?
I'm here.
This girl disappears
when she gets nervous.
I see!
First, we'll strengthen your core!
10-minute plank!
Eek!
S-Santhi...
Lubnacchi?
Thank you for becoming...
...my friend.
Lubnacchi?!
You there! Are you alright?!
That's all for today's training!
Lubnacchi, you alive?
I'm a Ghost.
Oh yeah!
Um...
Would you like some water?\
Rougia
Singer of FL∀MMe-Glam
Ah, much thanks!
I'm coming back to life...!
Oh~ Rougia, you've already debuted?
Yeah. I'm the singer for
a unit called FL∀MMe-Glam.
S-Senpai...
I only enrolled a little before you did.
Man, I wanna debut already, too.
W-W-Will I ever be able to debut?
Sympathy!
She showed me footage of
FL∀MMe-Glam's live performance.
Eek!
I get really excited when I hold a mic.
Looking down, sighing,
hiding my true feelings
Every time i step forward,
even if i'm trembling,
I can't lie to my desire of change!
It's surely a distant dream right now,
but i want to chase it together!
Even if our futures are different colors,
Let's paint them with the same dream.
Because you are the one who gives me courage!